One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
We were able to escape from the set course
along the boundary between sky and sea.
Now we're rowing our way
to a hidden adventure at the dark bottom of the sea.
Doesn't it sound fun just thinking about it?
Let's travel all through the worldwide seas,
raising our battle cry.
If you've made up your mind, let the signal for departure
ring out.
That feeling we had when we set sail
is something I'll never forget.
Because of that
nothing will be able to scare me...
Now, as the trip approaches, our racing heartbeats
engrave a rhythm of adventure in our shy hearts.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
Fill your empty heart with dreams.
Spread your wings.
If you color your heart with the blowing wind
you will move on.
Get all the treasures
while laughing out loud.
Give them all out at a big party
making a splash...
The Crew's Annihilation!
Oars vs. Nightmare Luffy
Hold!
I can't-
Good work, Robin!
Is this how you intend to stop me?
Such a pointless act.
Brick Bat!
Robin-chan!
Veinte Fleur!
Twenty Flowers
Calendula!
Marigold
Robin!
How dare you hurt Robin-chan!
Moriah's shadow?
Now then, shall we fight to decide which is the best ability?!
This hold of yours is quite effective!
I shouldn't pay attention to his shadow.
If I bring down the body, the shadow will surely be annihilated as well.
Cuatro Manos!
Four Hands
H-Hey, you!
What're you-
Stop!
Clutch!
She did it!
You're amazing, Robin!
Hey, Robin! Look out for the shadow behind you!
What is Moriah doing here?!
Pretty close.
But it's a shame for you,
I can switch places with Doppelman any time I want.
Switch places?
Then, the one over there is...
Your judo armlock won't work on my shadow.
Yes, the same shadow that was here a while ago!
Robin-cha-
Now it's three down!
Robin's shadow was also taken!
I don't have a marionette for you right now, so I might just keep you with me.
Diable Jambe...
Devil Leg
You filthy bastard!
Give back Robin-chan's shadow!
Extra Hachis!
Highest-Rate Mincemeat
Brick Bat!
He switched places with his shadow again?!
Then, that means...!
Moriah's back in Oars' stomach again!
And now you're back to where you started.
Damn it, Master!
Stop messing with my fight!
My bad, Oars.
I got a bit carried away it seems.
I better finish off that woman.
Rubber...
He's able to stretch again!
No way!
Robin isn't conscious anymore!
Sanji! Robin! Run for it!
Bazooka!
Diable Jambe...
Frit Assorti!
Fried Assortment
He deflected it!
Now is our chance!
Take Robin-chan away!
Leave it to me!
Hey!
Sanji!
Zoro!
Chopper, what're you doing there?!
I was searching for Oars' cause of death five hundred years ago.
Cause of death?
Aim for his right arm!
This is not Oars' original arm!
Although it was restored by Hogback's amazing skills,
The joints show remains of terrible frostbite.
I can't tell for sure, but...
The cause of his death, 500 years ago, was most likely of freezing.
Despite being such a monster, he was no match to the forces of nature.
He froze to death as he wandered through the Ice Country.
The reason is that, even five hundred years ago, Oars was still...
Naked!
I can't believe we're losing to such an idiot!
Zombies may not feel pain, but the damage received remains.
All of the attacks he's received have been accumulating!
If we get rid of this arm, his strength will be halved!
Anyway, aim for this spot-
Quit babbling, you tiny man on my shoulder!
Chopper!
A zombie like you can't even realize how much that punch just now hurt your body!
He's in my hand.
With my current size, the gap in your fist feels like a huge cave!
Rumble...
Jumping Point!
Arm Point!
Chopper!
Nice job!
Let me give you a hand!
Sanji, I'm counting on you!
Armée de l'Air...
Air Force
Carving Hoof!
Roseo Shoot!
Cherry Blossom Shoot
You bastard!
Why do you insist on attacking the same spot?!
If it didn't work before, it won't work now!
It will work.
Pain is a signal to protect the body.
Not having it... doesn't make you any stronger at all!
Say whatever you want then!
Hey, it's dangerous, you two!
Get away quickly!
Rubber...
Damn it.
This is bad.
Gatling!
Sanji!
Chopper!
Another two...
Everyone... is being eliminated.
Damn it!
Four!
Five!
And only three remain!
Only... three remain.
Now, hurry up and crush them, Oars!
He's coming!
It's useless!
We can't possibly win against such a monster!
We're out of options!
What should we do?!
Usopp!
I'll create an opening.
I see!
I get it!
Alright then!
What do you mean, Usopp?!
Rubber...
Pistol!
Damn it!
Three Swords Style...
Demon Crow!
Did we do it!?
Did it work!?
Usopp, now is-
Attacking my right arm again?!
I've told you countless times; it won't work!
I'll get rid of you!
He disappeared!
Zoro!
Hey, Oars!
Look this way!
What?
Something... went into my mouth.
Usopp, what was that?
I did it.
I finally did it!
I finally made Oars swallow the salt!
Salt?
What of it?
I see, you didn't know.
Salt is the zombie's weakness!
Look! This is it for Oars!
Luffy's shadow is coming out!
Get purified, monstrous zombie!
The victory is mine!
Come out!
Why... is Moria's shadow...?
I'm protecting him from the inside!
What a simpleton.
Celebrating victory prematurely.
Did you actually think I wouldn't have a countermeasure for such a weakness?
Idiot!
Damn!
I think this is yours, Long-nose!
Usopp!
No good, the salt!
The salt Brook gathered for us!
Damn! Damn!
Making fun out of us!
Rubber...
Stamp!
Usopp!
Stop!
Stop it!
Usopp!
Not yet!
Smash him to pieces!
The same goes for the woman!
Crush them! Crush them!
Crush every single one of them!
Crush the ones who're already unconscious too!
There's still a bit of breath in them!
Smash them until they're no longer recognizable as humans!
Hey, big idiot.
What do you think you are stomping?
Nobody is under your foot.
Who're you?
I'm... I'm...
Was I saved?
I don't know what happened, but...
Thanks for helping us out ther-
No way!
Monkey D. Luffy!
L-Lu-
Lu-
Luffy!?
Which part?!
You somewhat...
You somewhat resemble him, but...!
Is it really you?!
Are you serious!?
It is... really me.
Well, your way of talking matches.
What happened to you?!
Does he also have the ability to transform?
Or...?
Was everyone defeated?
Y-Yes.
Except for us, everyone else got beaten up by that monster.
I see.
Step aside.
Step aside!?
Don't you understand, Luffy?!
That zombie possesses your shadow!
Furthermore, his body can stretch and perform your techniques too!
It doesn't matter.
Crush them, Oars.
Of course!
Rubber...
Here he comes!
Rifle!
The only Luffy...
is me!
Something is flying this way!
What is it?
A rain cloud?
No way!
It's Oars!
Damn it...
What?!
He's doing it!
He's fighting equally with Oz!
Now is our chance! Start searching!
H-Hey!
I found a member of the Crew of Hope!
Here too!
What a horrible wound.
Everyone was beaten up badly.
This guy was beaten to the point that his bones are visible!
It's dangerous to leave them here.
Take them somewhere safe, quickly!
What are they doing?
There's so many of them.
Are they zombies?
What're they gonna do with Zoro and the others?!
Let's hurry back!
Hey, hey!
What's going on here?
Oars is losing!
I can't believe such a monster is losing.
What's wrong, O-Oars?!
Hey! Have you heard?!
Moriah-sama is currently inside Oars' belly!
Then, the master of all the zombies in Thriller Bark is being beaten, along with the ultimate Special Zombie?!
What kind of joke is this?!
Oars... the legendary man who 500 years ago was called a demon!
And our master is a Royal Warlord of the Sea!
Gekko Moriah-sama!
What?!
So by stuffing Luffy with the shadows of
100 victims, you made him look like that?!
That's correct, Crew of Hope.
To be honest, we're surprised about how much power he has acquired!
But... that strength will only last 2 or 3 more minutes!
The shadows we placed in him will begin to leave his body!
We're sorry for messing with your captain, but...
We've entrusted him with all of our hope!
We want to be humans again!
He's our last hope!
It's nearly daybreak.
The fate of all the island's victims will be decided within the next few minutes.
We're counting on you, Nightmare Luffy.
The mansion is breaking apart!
Hurry and escape!
This is really amazing.
Alright!
Way to go, Luffy!
You bastard!
Insignificant scum!
Rubber...
Bullet!
Damn you, Oars!
Where did Straw Hat acquire such power?!
Damn!
I might get involved in this.
I better get out of the cockpit for no-
Rubber...
Pistol!
Battle Axe!
Rubber...
Storm!
Oars is being...!
Moriah-sama!
He's coming down, be careful!
The shadows... are coming out.
Hey, is Luffy gonna be alright?
Luffy!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Am I dreaming?
He won.
Yes, the Crew of Hope has done it!
Oars and Moriah have been defeated!
Everyone's shadow will return!
Thriller Bark...
has fallen!
Translation & initial timing, Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000, Feeso
Video editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, Halee
Raw provider, SOFCJ-Raws